[
    {
        "front": "はじめまして",
        "back": "Nice to meet you",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "わたし",
        "back": "I",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "です",
        "back": "is, am, are",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぞ",
        "back": "(Spoken while offering something)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "よろしく",
        "back": "Favors (Greetings)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "インド",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "じん",
        "back": "(Suffix for Nationality)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "インドじん",
        "back": "Indian",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんじん",
        "back": "Japanese",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごくじん",
        "back": "Chinese",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "アメリカじん",
        "back": "American",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "がくせい",
        "back": "Student",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんせい",
        "back": "Teacher, Professor",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きれい",
        "back": "Beautiful",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "たかい",
        "back": "Expensive",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろい",
        "back": "Wide",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ともだち",
        "back": "Friend",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃいん / かいしゃいん",
        "back": "Employee / Company Employee",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "はい",
        "back": "Yes",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "いいえ",
        "back": "No",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "さん",
        "back": "(Honorifics; “honorable Mr/Ms.”)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゃん",
        "back": "(Honorific for Kids and…)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "インド",
        "back": "India",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほん",
        "back": "Japan",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "アメリカ",
        "back": "America",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごく",
        "back": "China",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこく",
        "back": "Korea",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "フランス",
        "back": "France",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドイツ",
        "back": "Germany",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "イタリア",
        "back": "Italy",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ロシア",
        "back": "Russia",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "インドじん",
        "back": "Indian",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんじん",
        "back": "Japanese (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "アメリカじん",
        "back": "American",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごくじん",
        "back": "Chinese (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこくじん",
        "back": "Korean (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "フランスじん",
        "back": "French (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドイツじん",
        "back": "German (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "イタリアあじん",
        "back": "Italian (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ロシアじん",
        "back": "Russian (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ヒンディゴ",
        "back": "Hindi",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんご",
        "back": "Japanese (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいご",
        "back": "English",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうごくご",
        "back": "Chinese (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんこくご",
        "back": "Korean (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "フランスご",
        "back": "French (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドイツご",
        "back": "German (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "イタリアご",
        "back": "Italian (language)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ロシアご",
        "back": "Russian (citizen)",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "みっな さん",
        "back": "everyone, all of you",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "げんき",
        "back": "health, energy, vigor",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "あなた",
        "back": "You",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "インジニア",
        "back": "Engineer",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "いしゃ",
        "back": "Doctor",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "あの かた",
        "back": "That Person",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "どなた",
        "back": "Who",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "さくら",
        "back": "Name of a University",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがく",
        "back": "University",
        "chapter": "N5 C1"
    }
]